https://crfrankpopcorn.com/privacy-policy/

Shopping Cart
Cart:
0 items
$0.00
No products in the cart.
Home / Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
Effective Date: June 27, 2014
This Privacy Policy applies to personal and other information that may be collected when you interact with the Select Drink, Inc, which consists of (a) Select Drink, Inc. and its subsidiaries, including their respective businesses and operations (collectively, “Select Drink”); (b) businesses and operations managed or operated by Select Drink; (c) websites owned, operated and managed by Select Drink, including each website that links to this Privacy Policy, and any digital content stores operated by Select Drink (collectively, “Select Drink Websites”); and (d) Select Drink and digital devices (“Devices”), content, software and mobile applications (“Apps”).
Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a priority at Select Drink, and we believe that a single, comprehensive privacy policy that is straightforward and clear is in the best interests of our customers and our businesses.
By interacting with Select Drink in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of all your personal and other information as described.
These current privacy policies and the privacy practices described herein apply to personal information previously collected from you by Select Drink, Inc. and each of its subsidiaries, as well as personal information that they may collect from you in the future.
Select Drink reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, but you can be assured that, should it be necessary to do so, we will always do so in accordance with the Select Drink Privacy Principles of Clarity, Security and Integrity. You will be notified of any material changes to this Privacy Policy which are less protective of customer information prior to such changes becoming effective. We may notify you of these changes by email reminders, by notice on this site, or by other acceptable means. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Clarity: We strive to communicate clearly about your privacy and how we handle your personal information.
Security: We follow security standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information.
Integrity: We do not sell or rent your personal information and respect your preferences with respect to your personal information.
1. WHAT IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT
Depending on how you choose to interact with the Select Drink enterprise, we may collect personal information from you, for example your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card or bank account information, date of birth and other persistent identifiers that can be used to personally identify you. If you purchase or otherwise place orders for concessions products from Select Drink. We may also collect other personal information regarding your interaction with Select Drink Websites, Devices and Apps, including usage information, the items that you browse, purchase, download, read, watch and otherwise access, and your geographic location.
2. WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We collect your personal information in an effort to provide you with a superior customer experience and, as necessary, to administer our business. It allows us to provide you with easy access to our products and services, with a particular focus on the items and programs that may be of most interest to you. For more information as to why we collect personal information, please see the section below entitled: “How do we use your personal information?”
Your personal information also allows us to communicate with you about special offers, promotions, and other marketing programs and news that may be of interest to you. You always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from promotional emails by following the instructions included in each marketing email or by changing your preferences in your account. You may unsubscribe from mobile notifications by changing your settings in the Apps or on your Select Drink or third party device.
3. HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
(a) Information that you provide to us
As a general matter, you can browse in our stores and on the Select Drink Websites without submitting your personal information to us, although we may receive and collect certain personal information automatically, as outlined in Section 3(b) of this Privacy Policy, including site analytics regarding our websites, information your Internet browser automatically sends when you visit our websites, and information collected by cookies.
However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may need to provide us with your personal information. The most common of these circumstances include:
Making a purchase or placing an order
Creating an account
Using specific features of Select Drink Websites, Devices and Apps
Contacting customer service
Additional Select Drink Website, Device or App Features
Interacting with social networking sites
Entering a sweepstakes or contest
Signing up for promotional communications or using Invite-a-Friend
For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of each of these circumstances below.
Making a purchase or placing an order
When you make a purchase, place an order in our stores, place an order online or purchase, download, you may need to submit personal information to us.
Using specific features of Select Drink, Inc. Websites, Devices and Apps
Select Drink Websites, Devices and Apps may provide you with the ability to enter (either directly, or by authorizing Select Drink to download the information from a third party such as a social networking website) your information such as your contacts, calendar entries or photos, or images you may submit to us to help us locate products for you.
Contacting Customer Service
When you contact customer service, we may ask you to provide, or confirm, personal information so that we can better serve you.
Additional Website, Device or App Features
From time to time we may offer or provide new or additional Select Drink Website, Device or App features and functionality. Such features or functionality may request or require you to submit personal information to us in order to use such feature or functionality.
Entering a sweepstakes or contest
If you enter a sweepstakes or contest we offer, we may ask you to provide personal information so that we can consider your entry and, if you win, so that you may redeem your prize.
Interacting with social networking sites
Our Devices and Apps may provide you with the ability to enter (directly, or by authorizing us to download the information from a third party such as a social networking site or application) personal information such as contacts or lists of friends. These or related applications may also allow you to provide information directly to social networking sites including information about your purchases, physical location, or comments. However, we will not provide any of your information to social networking sites without your express consent.
(b) Information automatically collected
There are circumstances in which we automatically receive and collect information from you. The most common sources of this information include:
Web server logs
Cookies
Pixel tags or clear Graphics Interchange Format files, known as GIFs
Third party web analytics services
Targeted advertising
Your Device or Apps you use, including geolocation
Wireless networks operated by Select Drink in retail stores
Social networking sites
Your college or university
Business partners, contractors, and other third parties
For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of each of these circumstances below.
Web server logs
When you visit a Select Drink Website, our web servers may automatically log information that your browser sends us. For example, we may receive and collect: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the date and time you access the Select Drink Website; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Select Drink Website. We may also collect information regarding search queries run on the Select Drink Website. We use this information to monitor the usage of the Select Drink Websites and as necessary for our business.
Cookies
Like many online retailers, we and/or our third party providers use cookies to recognize you as you use or return to the Select Drink Websites. This is done so that we can personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience. “Cookies” are small files that we place on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about your activities on a Select Drink Website. Cookies help us to: (1) speed navigation, keep track of items in your shopping bag and provide you with content that is tailored to you; (2) remember information you gave us so that you do not have to re-enter it; (3) determine the effectiveness of some of our and our third party partners’ marketing efforts and communications; and (4) monitor the total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of banners displayed.
Browsers are typically set to create cookies automatically. You can choose to have your browser notify you when cookies are being written to your computer or accessed, or you can disable cookies entirely. If you disable cookies, however, you will not be able to place items in a Select Drink Website shopping bag, and therefore you will not be able to place an order with us online. Also, by not using cookies, some Select Drink Website features and services may not function properly.
Pixel tags or clear GIFs
We may use sensing technologies that use pixel tags or clear GIFs (which are also called web beacons). These technologies allow us to determine the effectiveness of our e-mail and advertising and marketing efforts. For this purpose, we tie the pixel tags and clear gifs to personally identifiable information. We may also collect information regarding the links within such marketing materials that you click on and purchase statistics regarding items you buy following receipt of such marketing.
Third party web analytics services
We work with third party service providers, including but not limited to Google Analytics, to help us better understand how you use the Select Drink Websites. These third party service providers will place cookies on your computer to collect information such as how you were referred to the Select Drink Website, how you navigate around the Select Drink Website, what you purchase and what traffic is driven by various marketing methods. This information will help us to better serve you and provide you with more personalized information and product offerings. We do not allow third party service providers to collect your credit card information, e-mail address or password information. These third party service providers may only use your personal information to perform services for us and may not share your personal information with anyone else, or use it for any other purpose, except on an aggregated, non-personally identifiable basis.
To learn more about the privacy practices of Google, you may review its privacy policy located here. To disable the Google Analytics cookie and other third party web analytics service provider cookies, you can choose to have your browser notify you when cookies are being written to your computer or accessed, or you can disable cookies entirely.
Targeted advertising
We may partner with third party advertising networks that collect IP addresses, unique device identifiers (UDIDs), browser type, operating system, time zone, country, referring pages, and other information through the use of cookies, web server logs and pixel tags on Select Drink Websites, Apps, emails and on third party websites and emails. They use this information to provide you with advertisements that are customized to your particular preferences, including for companies that are not affiliated with us. You may see these advertisements on Select Drink Websites and third party websites. We may use this process to help us manage and improve the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. If you would like to learn more about the third party advertisers that may be aware of the fact that you visit Select Drink Websites, and to understand your opt-out choices, please click here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Please understand that Select Drink does not control these third party cookies, and you should check the privacy policies of third party advertising networks to see whether and how it uses cookies.
Your Device or Apps you use, including geolocation
When you use a Device or our Apps, we automatically collect information through the Device or App when it is connected to the Internet. For example, we may receive and collect information concerning device registration, settings, usage, firmware version, signal strength, search queries, network interaction, the name of the network from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the device you are using, unique device identifiers (UDIDs), downloads, sideloaded content, configuration, or service information relating to any malfunction of the Device or App. This may include information regarding your reading, viewing and activity behavior on such Devices or Apps, such as books or videos opened, date and time of use, time elapsed, page turns, bookmarks, annotations, customer reviews, and quiz or test answers.
In addition, to provide location-based services on Devices or through Apps, Select Drink and third party application providers may automatically collect real-time geographic location information or other location-based information about you and your Device or other mobile device on which the App is installed. This information may be used to provide certain device or application functionality or to offer, provide and improve products and services.
Wireless networks operated by Select Drink in retail stores
When you connect your computer or mobile device to wireless networks operated by Select Drink at store locations, we may collect information concerning your location, unique device identifiers (UDIDs), date and time of access and information regarding your interaction with the Select Drink enterprise through Select Drink Websites, Devices or Apps as permitted by this Privacy Policy.
Social networking sites
We may provide you the ability to sign into a Select Drink Website or App using a social networking account such as a Facebook, Twitter or Google account, or use your social networking accounts to share information from Select Drink Websites, Devices or Apps. In these cases, as well as when you use a Select Drink app on a social networking site or choose to join (or “like”) a Select Drink page on a social networking site, the social networking site may provide us with certain information about you, including but not limited to your contacts and other “likes”. Please see the privacy policy for the applicable social networking site to learn more about how these sites share your personal information.
Business partners, contractors, and other third parties
We may collect personal information and other information about you from business partners, contractors and other third parties. This includes, but is not limited to, instances in which you affirmatively authorize third parties to provide us with information. Such information may be collected via, but not limited to, software applications that you download or use on your Device or that otherwise allow you to interact with the Select Drink enterprise.
4. HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Select Drink uses your personal information across our enterprise to provide you with a superior customer experience and, as necessary, to administer our businesses. For example, we use your personal information to:
Provide you with products, services and information across the Select Drink enterprise, including product and subject recommendations and other information in Select Drink retail stores, through emails from our businesses, and on the Select Drink Websites and online interactive communities, your Devices, Digital Content, Apps and software, and display associated content and advertising;
Administer our programs;
Provide customer service in stores, by telephone and online;
Conduct research and perform analysis in order to measure, maintain, protect, develop and improve our products and services;
Administer sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys and provide appropriate notifications;
Communicate with you about special offers, events, or new products or services that may be of interest to you;
Customize and enhance the Select Drink Websites and advertising;
Make communications necessary to notify you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues; and
Manage our business.
5. WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a priority at Select Drink. Select Drink DOES NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES.
Please note that your data may be transferred to or shared with a third party as part of a sale, merger, or acquisition of Select Drink or one of its affiliates (see “Sales, Mergers, and Acquisitions” below).
Select Drink shares your personal information with:
Other entities within the Select Drink enterprise. Select Drink, Inc. owns and operates other operations and businesses and we may share your personal information with our other business units and operations, even if such business units or operations are sold.
Partners. We provide personal information to our partners that provide product and service offerings or technologies that we think may be of interest to you. Our partnerships may also result in products and services that allow you to publish Digital Content that may be shared with our partners. We may offer you the opportunity to opt-in to receive information from our partners, which may result in your personal information being shared with our partners. The use of your information by our partners and their vendors and contractors will be subject to the privacy policies of our vendors once such information is transferred.
Service providers, subcontractors and agents who perform services on our behalf. We provide personal information to third party service providers, subcontractors, and agents that work under contract on our behalf to provide certain services. These third parties do not have the right to use personal information we provide to them in any way that is not authorized by Select Drink. They are contractually obligated to use such information only as necessary to assist us and to maintain the confidentiality and security of such information.
Third party providers of products and services. These are third parties that provide products and services you may purchase or request from or through us. These third parties do not have the right to use personal information we provide to them in any way that is not authorized by Select Drink. They are contractually obligated to use such information only as necessary to assist us and to maintain the confidentiality and security of such information.
Third party membership programs. We work with certain third party entities to help them administer their own membership or rewards programs by providing them with purchasing information about their customers who make purchase from Select Drink. We disclose only the information that is necessary to make these third party programs work and to support your membership in them. This information usually includes your name and e-mail address as well as the dollar amount of the purchases made at Select Drink. We require such entities to obtain your consent before we provide them with this information, which they usually do as part of their own membership or participation rules.
Credit card companies. Credit card transactions are handled by third party financial institutions and their vendors and contractors who receive credit card numbers and other personal information from us to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions. Although Select Drink’s treatment of this information is governed by this policy, the use of your information by the third party financial institutions and their vendors and contractors will be subject to their own privacy policies.
Law enforcement officials and as required by law. Select Drink may release personal information to third parties when we determine, in our judgment, that it is necessary to (a) comply with the law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b)enforce or apply the terms of any of our policies or user agreements; or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Select Drink, our employees, our customers, users, or others.
Co-branded offerings. In some instances, we may offer a service or feature that is co-branded by Select Drink and a third party company. If you provide information in connection with such co-branded service or feature, that information may be shared between Select Drink and the third party. Although Select Drink’s treatment of the information is governed by this policy, the third party’s treatment of your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy
Other websites operated by Select Drink. In some instances, we may operate a Select Drink Website on behalf of a third party. If you provide information in connection with a Select Drink Website operated by Select Drink on behalf of a third party, that information may be shared between Select Drink and the third party. Although Select Drink’s treatment of the information is governed by this policy, the third party’s treatment of your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy.
Sales, mergers, and acquisitions. If Select Drink becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, restructuring, reorganization, or any form of sale or other disposition of some or all of its assets, personal information and your transaction history may be provided to the entities and advisors involved subject to a confidentiality agreement, and we will provide notice to you at your email address on file before any personal information is finally transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Such a transaction may involve us (i) retaining the right to continue to use transferred personal information in addition to the right of the transferee to use such information, and (ii) engaging in additional transfers of personal information (including new personal information) with the transferee from time to time following such a transaction.
6. HOW DO WE SECURE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We take significant and appropriate security measures, including physical, technological and procedural measures, to help to safeguard your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure. In addition, we use industry-standard technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology in the transmission of certain sensitive personal information, designed to prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information, and, as technology develops, we intend to take additional measures to improve security.
We want you to feel confident whenever you visit us in our stores, on the Select Drink Websites, or use Select Drink Devices or Apps. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information, you must remember that the Internet is a global communications vehicle open to threats, viruses and intrusions from others and so we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that we will be able to protect your personal information at all times and in all circumstances.
7. HOW DO WE RESPECT YOUR CHOICES ABOUT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
You may choose to opt out from receiving marketing and promotional communications from Select Drink at any time by following the instructions below.
For Select Drink: At any time, a customer may choose to opt-out of the receipt of any promotional communications by clicking on the opt-out link provided at the bottom of each email and following the instructions.
Even if you opt-out of receiving promotional communications, you may continue to receive emails and notifications relating to order confirmations, back order notifications, membership information, and/or other business-related communications.
Targeted Advertising
You may choose to opt out of collection of automatically collected information, including cookies, targeted advertising, by following the instructions given in Section 3(b) above, or by using the functionality in your browser to reject cookies.
Online Community Users
Select Drink provides you with the ability to access, correct, change or request deletion of the personal information in your community profile(s) at any time by following the instructions below. We will respond to all access requests within 30 days. However, you cannot currently change your profile name although you may re-register and choose a new name. Please be advised that Select Drink may archive information it collects on its community and visitors. Additionally, by participating in the Select Drink online interactive community, and using Select Drink’s various interactive offerings, including, the submission of customer reviews, you agree to receive communications from Select Drink, other users, and moderators related to the provision of these services.
8. WHOM DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS?
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at webmaster@selectdrink.com or call customer service at 1-314-731-4500.
9. WHAT OTHER INFORMATION ABOUT SELECT DRINK’S PRIVACY POLICY WOULD I WANT TO KNOW?
Policies for Minors, including children under the age of 13
Select Drink is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations regarding the collection, storage and use of personal information of Minors under the age of 13, including the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.
Except as noted below : (i) our products and services are marketed for and directed towards purchase by adults or with the consent of adults; (ii) Individuals under the age of 18 (“Minors”) are not permitted to use Select Drink Websites or Apps without the supervision of a parent or legal guardian; (iii) we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account or to post personal information on the Select Drink Websites; and (iv) should we learn that someone under the age of 13 has provided any personal information to or on any of the Select Drink Websites, we will remove that information as soon as possible.
If we direct certain Devices features or Apps to Minors who may be under the age of 13, we require the parent or legal guardian to provide verifiable consent to such Minor’s use of our products and services and our collection of personal information in connection with such use. In these cases, we require validation of credit card information already on file with us and we will then e-mail the master account holder to give notice that we have received such consent. If no credit card information is on file, or if the credit card is invalid, we will not register that you have consented. With your consent, we may collect, use and share information regarding Minors under the age of 13 consistent with this Privacy Policy. Please see the sections above for detailed information on how we do so.
If you are a parent or guardian who believes that your Minor under the age of 13 has submitted personal information or other information to us without your consent, please contact webmaster@selectdrink.com. Once we verify that you are the parent or legal guardian, at your request, we will promptly provide to you information regarding what, if any, personal information we have collected about your child and how it has been used or shared. We will, at your request, remove personal information about your child from its database and instruct our affiliates and third party partners to do the same.
Data retention policy
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Accessing your information
You have the right to ask us not to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes. You also have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies rectified. Please note that, as permitted by law, we may charge a nominal fee for information requests and may require you to prove your identity. Following a request, we will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you in our files. Please address written requests and questions about this to webmaster@selectdrink.com. We will respond to all access requests within 30 days.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request a notice from us describing which categories of personal information we have shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes within the last calendar year, and the name and address of such parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please send an email to webmaster@selectdrink.com with “California Privacy Rights Request” in the subject line.
Important information about third party devices, ISPs, websites and applications
This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Select Drink enterprise. Whenever you click on links and banners on any Select Drink Website that take you to a third party website or you use, download or install third party software applications onto your Device, your use of those third party websites and/or software will be subject to the third party’s privacy policies, not Select Drink’s. Additionally, please note that when using Select Drink Websites or Apps, third party mobile device manufacturers and internet service providers (ISPs) may collect personal information about you and your use of such third party products and services will be subject to the third party’s privacy policies.
In addition, our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Select Drink. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
Information collected from visitors from outside the United States
If you are visiting Select Drink or a Select Drink Website from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information will be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. Additionally, Select Drink may transfer your personal information to other countries, for example because a server or third party service provider is located there. The data protection and privacy laws of other countries, including the United States, may not afford you the same level of protection as those in your own country. Select Drink will take appropriate steps to protect your information.
Terms of Use
Any dispute between you and us regarding the privacy of your personal information is subject to this Privacy Policy and the terms of use or terms of service applicable to our product or service you use, including limitation on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Missouri.
Contact Information
The address for Select Drink is 5757 N Lindbergh Blvd, Hazelwood, MO 63042.
Copyright 2016 C.R. Frank Popcorn; All Rights Reserved. Website by Blue's ArtHouse Graphics & Web Design.
